Guide to the Griswold-Brewster Oral History Project, Yale University
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Audiotapes, 1990-1992; Series III
  - Wasserman, Elga, 1992 May 7; audiocassette (Box 222)
  - Wegener, Peter, 1992 July 20; audiocassette (Box 223)
  - Wegener, Peter, 1992 July 20; audiocassette (Box 224)
  - Weiss, Paul, 1992 May 28; audiocassette (Box 225)
  - Westerfield, H. Brad, 1991 October 28; audiocassette (Box 226)
  - Whiteman, Harold B.
    - 1991 Mar 22, audiocassette (Box 227)
    - 1991 May 2, audiocassette (Box 228)
  - Wilkinson, John, 1992 May 19; audiocassette (Box 229)
  - Wilkinson, John, 1992 May 19; audiocassette (Box 230)
  - Williams, Frank
    - 1990 Sep 24, audiocassette (Box 231)
    - 1991 Oct 11, audiocassette (Box 232)
  - Wilder, Amos, 1990 October 23; audiocassette (Box 233)
  - Wolff, Mary, 1992 April 9; audiocassette (Box 234)
  - Woodward, C. Vann, 1991 November 6; audiocassette (Box 235)
  - Zanger, Mark, 1992 April 7; audiocassette (Box 236)
  - Zweig, Felix, 1991 November 8; audiocassette (Box 237)